Doraemon
It's good if it's so
If it can come to true it'll b nice
Different dreams
all can be arrived
The mysterious pocket
will compass it for you
I want to fly freely
Come on, use the dragonfly
Ah~Ah~Ah~ I love Doraemon most
(Go forward the devil road)
I'm awake
I'll become a great man
I'll benefit the society
I've decided!
Nobita, have some cake
No, thank you, it's for you
Nobita said he didn't have cake?
The books of great man
He'd seen it
He's easily affected
Excuse me
It comes
Little bros, is your mom in
I'll ask her to come here, please wait
Mom, there's a guest
Troublesome, what'll I do
What's the matter with you
My contact lens is lost
It's bad,
let me help you to look for it
Little bros, it's very expensive
Sorry
Impossible
What're you saying
You're so charming,
you'd wear diamond at least
I'm shy
Look at this one,
it's as beautiful as you
Mom
What's up?
I help other to look for it
but I stamped on it
No way
Your pocket money will be decreased
from next month
I wanted to do a good deed originally
I'll not be upset
Great men all grew up in trouble
I'll not say uncle, I'll work hard
Nobita, come over
I've something to ask you
To ask me? OK
I'm glad to if it'll benefit mankind
I'm in bad mood now
Let me kick you
How do you say that
Don't you want
to be beneficial to people
It's better
You'd not do too much
I'll borrow someone's handkerchief...
Thank you
Lady-killer
Why does it become so
It's painful
Throw it to me
No, I won't do that!
No, I must do good deed
I'll throw it to you
Where will throw it?
It's a rough luck
It fits ladies most
We can allow you 60% discount
60% discount?
I dare not say that
mom, I beg you to compensate the glass
You can buy the sparkler of 0.5million
with 0.2 million
How do you like it
But...
You'd decrease 100,000 at least...
Let's call it a deal! 100,000 Yuan!
I got my salary yesterday,
it's just 100,00 Yuan
Nobita!
Be careful in the future
What do you think of it?
Are you doing a good deed?
I'm useless
I can benefit people nothing
I think there's something wrong
with him who wants to be a great man
Right, since I'll be scolded
for whatever I did
It's better to do bad things
I'll do bad deed particularly
No, don't do that
It's troublesome, we'd find a way
There's not a way
Good kid commander
It's good, you can't do anything bad
if you put on it
It's nothing
I'll do that if I like to
I must do something bad
You wait to look
Jian, how dared you bully me just now
I'm sorry
Nobita
Nobita!
You saved me
I didn't mean to do that
I'll not give it up
I'll go to harm Shizuka
It's painful
There're bees in it
Thank you, Nobita
Damn, I want do something bad
This hoop...
I can't take it off
I've said you can't do anything bad
No, I must do
I'll break the glass!
Look, someone“ come out
to ca“ your names
Nobody comes out
It smells terrible
The fire in the stove is put off
and gas comes out
you're poisoned by gas
Call for the ambulance
You saved me
Thank you, thank you...
Give up, whatever you do
people will be grateful to you
No, I'll be scolded this time
for I stole the money
Slightly...
Nobita!
Thank you, thank you...
It's lucky you take the money away
Mom's really happy
Later, police came and took him away
I almost buy a glass ball
with 100,00 Yuan
It seems that I can't do bad deeds
I'll try my best to do what I can
Doraemon, where's my cake
Didn't you say you gave it to me
No! It's mine! Give it to me!
(The medicine of boy students
and girl students)
It's finished
The new flower drum
I made with my heart
Let's call it butterfly
Shizuka will be comfortable to see it
It's finished, it's finished
It spreaded out
I can't make it out
Shit
You cry because it spreaded out
You'd play boy's game
I sold football to you last time
But you lent it to your friend
Dad feel shameful for you
I'll go
Come on, come over, run
Go ahead!
That rough game doesn't fit me
Boy's game, girl's game,
who stipulated it?
Is there a law which prevent boys
to play flower drum
If most boys play it
It'll become boys' game
Right
It's interesting, have a try
The medicine of boy students
and girl students
and girl students?
The medicine which can make boys
like girls
and make girls like boys
Spread it nearby
Wait, Doraemon
It's good
Will it really be effective
Great
Go Great
OK, move! This way!
It didn't change
It'll work soon Wait and look
OK, here's OK, come on
It's painful
It's too much
What're you doing
It'll be OK if you kick it back
It's too much
You're always crying,
are you a boy student
I think you'd not say so
Right
You're too rough
Right, apologize to me
Be quick to make an apology
What're you doing
you bully me together
OK! OK!
Look, it works
It's all because you play football
Will you play the flower drum,
let me teach you
How can Nobita do that
Will you skip OK
I like making moppet better
Let's go, move
Shizuka
I think out a new flower drum,
let me teach you
It's so at first
And do it like this then
Sorry, I'm not interested in it
The ball is good
Lend it to me
Let's play football
Nice
ls the medicine of boy students
and girl students effective
Then Shizuka who's like a girl...
I'll go, move!
Which side will you join
OK
It's painful
Are you OK
It's egregious
Boy students are always so boring
they like cry very much
Let's go, move, move
I'm back
What're you saying
How can boy play football
Persuade him
or it'll be troublesome
Mom
Doraemon, become what it was
No, I can't, it'll work for a whole day
Then will I play with them for a day?
Don't read newspaper when you have meal
(Pengpeng Leaf)
There's a family there
We're lost traveler,
may we stay here for a night
I never thought we could have wine
and dinner on the top of the mountain
It's like dreaming
The house disappeared
We're cheated by the fox
The dinner last night's leaf and mud
The people before is foolish
Do you believe
that fox will cheat people
It's true
The fox now has degraded
The fox will give out electric wave
when it meets danger
When people realize it, they're cheated
Really It's a joke
Damn Wait...
The students in the future
will do such experiment
Pengpeng Leaf
Put the leaf on the head like this
and the electric wave will come out
from the head
Lend it to me
No
They're made according to the brain
of the fox and the dog
Wait
The dog and the fox are both Canidae
What's the black art?
It's natural to fail
To cheat is a common way for
small animals to protect themselves
But lucky dogs don't need it
ls there an unlucky dog
Yeah, what a poor dog
The Xiaoban of that family, its owner
never took it to have a walk
It has to stay in the kennel
And it doesn't have enough food
If you give it some cake,
you'll be scolded
He said we made him lose face
Damn! Hum!
Look, he'll beat the dog
if he's unhappy
He did too much
Will this leaf do any help
I don't know Let's wait
This is the home of Violence
Why did the ball fall down
the boring place
Violence is the man's surname
He's atrocious,
so nobody will speak with him
I don't know if it matters
Be careful in the future
Hey! Who's it!
Deserve it!
What
Why does he become as the same as me
It's very flimflam!
It's OK in this way
I'm cheated
Xiaoban's so happy
It's the first time for it
to get freedom
Shit!
If you give the ball to us,
we'll allow you to join
Really
Will Violence...
Damn! Untie the chain!
Although I have feet, I can't walk
Did you steal the homer?
Well done, Violence
You run very fast
He's a dog, of course he runs fast
He's very happy to run freely
Remember, Xiaoban
I'll revenge
Shit!
You scored again, great
You're excellent
You must join in us
This may be the revenge of Xiaoban
I bullied it too much in the past
Shall I do it in all my life?
It happened before...
Xiaoban
He enjoyed himself for a day
I don't what it'll be in the future
If it goes home, it'll be bullied again
He's in a fog, isn't he
Beat it! Beat it!
It's like what I often did before,
beat me
Xiaoban
It's time for dinner
Where's that child
(The Forgotten Iron Hammer)
General
Nobita, wait, one time is OK
No way! I don't know you!
Mom, what's up
Morning
Who're you, uncle?
It seems that I've met you
I didn't raise such Pengpeng fox
I'm not Pengpeng fox
It means
Here's not your home
Who's this man
The man said he'd forgotten what he did
including his name, address, work, etc
It's fugue
Yes, so I've to ask
one family after another
Here's not your home, I never saw you
But we're alike, aren't we relatives
I've nothing to do with you
Maybe...
I'll can police if you don't go
Aren't you my grandpa?
You're kidding
Uncle, cheer up
You're hungry
Bring me another bowl of meal
It's the tenth one
Which is more, ten bowls or three bowls
You forget the number, uncle
Think over the clue
No way! I can recall nothing!
Doraemon
I want to help him, but...
OK! Let's use that one!
OK, there's no problem
OK, I'll take it out
This is the forgotten hammer
It can beat the lost memory out
The memory is like the drawer
the fugue is like the drawer
can't be opened
So if you beat the brain like this,
the memory will run out
You're really Doraemon
But if you do that wrongly
it'll have side effect
Will you have a try
It's terrible
You try first, I'll try
if there's no problem
I'll try, don't get angry
Beat it slightly
Look, his memory comes out
He fell down from the Tokyo Tower
Did I lost because that shock?
So you can forget
Let's see forward
The man often met misfortune
What's uncle on earth?
OK, let him remember where he lives
Do you live in the castle
Right, I remember,
I really lived in the castle
No wonder... I see
He's a rich man living in a big house
He's often sniped by bad apples
It's so
I really have the sense
after hearing what you said
The house like castle
It's easily to be found
OK
I'll give you 1 million Yuan
if you find it
Hah~
Take care
I can't find it
OK, go to ask them
It's settled
Castle
I've never been there
He's rich...
He's very rich
Aunt, I'll give you 100,00 Yuan
Thank you
Right, isn't supper ready?
You'd had it just now
There's not now
OK, I'll go out to have something
Uncle
What's up
Will you go to our home to have dinner
This is tea
This washrag
I'll give you 1 million Yuan each
We're alike
Maybe we're relatives
I've nothing to do with you
I heard you live in a luxury house
I want to have a look
OK, you may come
Ah?
Is it a castle
Yeah, it's only a castle
Once more
No, my interest is
to imitate the beggar
You're cheating me
Go out
Curious, beat it once more
Don't run
Uncle's...
the wanted person?
Right... maybe
Hey, I'll beat you
Stop! Don't run!
We found the castle
It's only a place
where people take photos
That's...
I'm a big lady-killer
It's dangerous, there's a problem
I must find out uncle's really ID
this time
He's a monk
He's a patrol of space
He's a arrester in the ancient time
Ah... Who am I...
I see, uncle's an actor
Where's that 1 million Yuan
What'll we do
It's gone
Everyone's crazy
They're too greedy
( Happy Life)
It's dull
ls there any interesting thing
Something which makes the world happy
No
I can't stand
Doraemon,
is there any interesting thing
Something which makes us laugh
No! I'm reading, don't shout
Don't say that cold words
I feel vapid, I want to be happy
I want to laugh
There's nothing interesting
Right, if you want to smile
You may use this tool
This is smiling earphone
Smiling earphone?
If you put it into your ear
you'll feel anything interesting
ls it OK to put it into ear?
How do you feel?
It's funny
It's very droll
No way
I can't bear it
ls it so funny?
I never heard such funny story
Boring... it's troublesome
It's funny...
The shortcoming of it is only the
man who wears it feels interesting
People around him
will think he's foolish
I'm sorry... I can't breathe
I feel relaxed
It's good to laugh
You'll not feel vapid every day
OK
Wait, come here
I've something to talk to you
Sit down here
It's the first time for mom
to lose face like this today
It's all because you don't work hard...
No way
It's too funny, I can't breathe
Mom, don't say that
Nobita!
It's painful
But...
I'm dying
Tiresome, even the dog is droll
Help, help, it's too funny
It suitable to you, madam
ls it so?
How about“? Nu
It'd be nice
Good
Really
Then try it there
Let's call it deal
I'm beautiful in whatever clothes
I'm greatly moved
Nobita
Suneo, do you have anything
Mom bought me this clothes, is it nice
Nothing interesting
Suneo, how do you like it,
is it beautiful
Nobita
What're you doing
It's droll
Don't make me angry
But...
It's really funny
It's the first time for me
to be bullied
Mom... Nobita
Shizuka, What's the matter with you
why you are crying here
The canary of our family died
Canary... died...
You're so cruel
Wait, wait
There's some reason
I hate you I split chums with you
Why do you say that?
Don't say that Wait
Ah?
Stop! Nobita!
Is other's misfortune droll
Hey! You!
It's interesting
ls it? You're such kind of man!
Shut up, Jian
I beg you, I'm sorry
it's terrible to laugh too much
I'll let you know result
of looking down upon others
Nobita, I'll beat you
Doraemon will know it'll be so
Give me that tool
Nobita, I heard one funny thing
There's a monkey with red ass somewhere
If you ask why the ass is red...
It's too noisy
I heard too much, shut up
(Space Mountain Tai, the forepart)
OK, Space Mountain Tai, go
Beat him, beat, beat
Come on, Space Mountain Tai
Space Mountain Tai!
Space Mountain Tai
Hah, we win
Space Mountain Tai won
it's funny
Doraemon,
do you feel it's interesting
It's bad
The story becomes longer and longer
What a mess
What did you say Don't say that
Space Mountain Tai is my hero
Who wants to fool Space Mountain Tai
please come over
Are you still in the kindergarten?
Doesn't everybody like to see it
I'm tired of it
It's vapid
I don't see that
You're so cruel
If you're really fans
you'd rescue
when we go down the mountain
Space Mountain Tai
Space Mountain Tai,
please sign your name for me
I'm your fan
Thanks
But...
We'll depart soon
Depart? Why?
The program may be stopped
The audience rating is always declining
Impossible! Why?
Because the cost is lower
Films become cheaper and cheaper
Then invest more capital
No clients will make ads
in the poor program
Although it's lonely,
there's still no way
Thank you for your help in the past
See you
It's rough-and-tumble
Use the tool which can improve
the audience rating
or Space Mountain Tai will stop
No
Doraemon
Anyway
I'll let him go on performing
Nobita, it's time for supper
There must be a good method
It's time for dinner
Don't be wordy,
I'm thinking over something
Really...
Isn't meal ready?
Don't shout, it's night
It's finished already
Finished? Why didn't you call me?
I asked you,
but you said it's too noisy
I'm very hungry
Take this
What, it's mealie pellet
Man can have it
It's used to tame animals
Animals which take the pellet
will be under control
Doraemon, I've got an great idea
Can't you go on performing
No, clients said they'd not invest
Then it'll stop
Please wait
You're the...of yesterday
It's OK if you make films without money
To imitate the world
of 100 million years ago
The fake dinosaur like the real one
They're all can be used free
Nonsense, there's no such a thing then
Superintendent, he's my fan
I think you can believe him
OK, I'll wait for you for a day
In either case there's no hope
150 million years ago
time
oi the Cretaceous period
Doraemon should go now
Look for the suitable dinosaur first
Feed it with pellet
and let it help photograph
How's it going, Doraemon?
How do you like that one?
Do you mean that dinosaur
Space Mountain Tai can sit on it
and shout
It's it's too ugly
It'll decrease the audience rating
You'd look for a big and violent one
I see, I'll meet an hour later
See you
I thought there're many dinosaur
at that time
The earth is so big
I still didn't find one till now
It's a pterosaur
Help
Doraemon, Doraemon
Doraemon!
No... no... no...
(Space Mountain Tai The post-part)
Doraemon!
Help, help
I thought I might die
The mealie pellet disappeared
and the dragonfly either
You're kidding
I'll be over when the dinosaur appears
It appears!
No! No! Help...
It's painful
No! Stop!
No, help, wait
Look there
Look here
It's tamed
I see
He ate the pellet I lost
Run, hah
We succeeded
Doraemon, it's Burundi
There're a huge crowd there
Really, great
Bring out more pellet
and the dragonfly too
Come on, eat it, hah
Get together here after finishing it
We got it
Great success!
I won't worry then
There're many dinosaurs
Wait
Don't others know the secret
of time machine
You didn't say that till now
How can I take him
to the Cretaceous period
OK, let's do it like this
Connect the outlet
of the convenient door
with the outlet of the time machine
Doraemon is very smart
Space Mountain Tai, there's no problem
R's Hague
It's impossible that you
lend us the world which's like
the real one and the rag roll
I'll go back
Since we've come, why...
No, it must be the monkey trick of kids
Sorry for keeping you waiting too long
The stage is in the yard
Let me tell you!
Nobita, you...
Space Mountain Tai, come to have a look
I'll go back
Superintendent, please wait
What do you want to do
You'd have a look at least
Don't say that
Superintendent
I beg you
It's because of the children that
Space Mountain Tai can last till today
I see
It's only one time, I'm very busy
This is...
I can't believe
ls it fake?
Are these all rag rolls
They're like the real ones
Will you don't ask so many questions?
Or I won't lend them to you
I see, I'll ask nothing
Thank you, Nobita
We'll make a good film
Space Mountain Tai, please shout
Great!
It becomes more charming
The audience rating is beyond 40%
I'll act as Space Mountain Tai
It'd be me, me
Great, everybody likes him again
Nobita
I'll work hard
(The Soul Machine)
I've had such childhood,
it's not like the real one
It's the most happy then
Nobita is very lively
Nobita, tidy them up quickly
OK, I'm doing it
Mom would not shout at me
when I was young
What a pain
The blood's running out, mom
What's up
I was tripped by a stone
It's painful
To put some slobber is OK
It's very painful...
Chut, you become
more and more tiresome
There's no such a thing
No, it's so
I want to go to my childhood
You can go now
But there's only once
Really?
The soul machine
Let the soul leave the body
and fix to me of past
Can't I return?
Time is set, no problem
Put this on your head
Go to your infant period
Oh, dear
Go to the memory sometime
I'll go to sleep now
Nobita, do you finish now
Why do you sleep here
You didn't tidy them, and always sleep
It's strange
Nobita, Nobita, what's wrong with you
Nobita!
I become an infant
I'm an infant, I'm an infant
Someone comes
Did you sleep well, baby
OK, it's time to have milk
Baby, are you hungry
You're so happy, come on, have milk
It's warm
I don't want to have milk but cola
You don't like cola, do you like cola
No wonder...
Dear
I'd not say cola
Nobita said he wanted to have cola
Impossible
He's too young to have cola
And Nobita can't speak
Are you dreaming, dear
Please come to have a look
Nobita, say Cola
Cola, dad
Do you hear, he said dad
It's surprising
Nobita, can you say Mom
Mom
Granny
It's the first time for me
to see such a clever baby
I'm greatly surprised Me too
He may become a scholar
They become glad
after I said only a few words
But I'd be careful
so that their hope won't be very high
Are you happy
It's nice to be an infant
I needn't walk myself
Well done, well done
Whatever I did, I'll be praised
and won't be scolded
You may roll freely
Nobita, it's time to go to bed
It's time to sleep at noon
Mom will sing you a lullaby
Baby, sleep...
Good baby... Go to sleep...
Nobita, Nobita, Nobita
You wake up
Mom
Great, I thought you'd died
You fell down to the ground,
and didn't breathe any longer
You worried me so much?
Sure, mom's greatly surprised
and my heart almost stop beating
And my knees are still trembling now
I catch a fever
Mom
I'm OK
She's greatly struck
Mom often worries about me
Her hair becomes silver
Of course it's hard-working
to have a child like you
I think so
Boob, what're you saying!
I'll go to see mom
Good idea
Mom, are you alright
She'll ill now
Boob, She's sleeping
I'm greatly scared
Right
Go to sleep...
It seems Nobita begins
to be grateful to his parents
Some faces are round
Some faces are long
Some faces are square
Some faces are triangular
Weeping Angry Fawning and requesting
You'll become a ghost who likes crying
But if you smile
Your face will become round